[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Will Gabby run again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "It's looking pretty good that she'll be in a position where she can make the decision to run for her seat again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "How did it start for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, it was -- for us, it was typical.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Could anything prepare you for that call?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, it's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pia"]}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "And you ring back to get more information, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Yes, so I wasn't even sure -- after I got off the phone with Pia, it was a very short conversation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Were you hearing the same kind of erroneous information?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 86, "question": "How did you find out that she was still alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "For a fact?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "So the airplane also had a phone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What is the first thing that you find there when you get there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well, it was a busy day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Were you getting any sense of how this was playing out around the world, or were you very much locked in that room now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I was pretty focused on what was going on with her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "When you saw her like that, if you're honest, looking back on it, did you fear then, you were never going to get your wife back in any kind of normal form?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "So, yes, part of me feared that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "LOCATION": ["Gabby"], "PERSON": ["Kirsten Gillibrand", "Debbie Wasserman Schultz"]}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Do you remember much of that time, or is that all just a blur to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Well, about 10 minutes after he walked out of the room, Kirsten Gillibrand and Debbie Wasserman Schultz, two of her very good friends from Congress, were there in the room with us, and they were talking to Gabby, you know, for a good amount of time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "And with Gabby, what was the moment for you when you thought for the first time, I may get my wife back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Even before she opened her eyes, she would -- you know, with her eyes closed, she took -- I took my ring off my finger once.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gabby"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "As she used to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "As she used to do, just like I'm doing here, and she would, you know, just -- you know very naturally, you know -- so you knew she was in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "``", "NN", ",", "''", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What was the first word that she spoke?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, it was reported that she said the word \"toast,\" which she did around that day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Were you there when she first said that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "EX", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I did -- yes, I was standing right there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "How does that feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, it feels great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "But are you going to get through it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "You can get through it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBG", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "And it was tough, hard, every tiny step of the way, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Well, you know, a lot of people have rehab that affects one part of their body, the relearning how to walk or relearning how to use their limbs or in her case, you know, the -- the speech.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "It's amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Did you know any of this before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "I didn't know any of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Were there particular songs or singers that seemed to have a particular effect?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, things she knew well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "So Don McLean has basically got a lot to be thanked for, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Don McLean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Megan Morrow"]}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "So Megan Morrow, the music therapist, would play some U2 and some -- I mean stuff that she's familiar with and likes to hear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "It hurts you, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "How did she react in the moment when you were able to finally tell her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Well, we had a plan that we would tell her things as she asked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "And how was she able to react to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, initially, she -- you know, she was -- she was shocked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "BONO, U2 VOCALIST: What's on your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Looking forward to coming home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Young Leaders Forum"], "LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "When did you first meet Gabby?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, I met her about seven years ago on a trip to China, with a group of young, Young Leaders Forum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Do you remember the first moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Yes, I remember seeing her for the first time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "And when did you realize this was actually potentially the woman you wanted to spend the rest of your life with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Well, we didn't go on a date until -- I went -- after that trip, I went over a year without seeing her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Of all the hot dates, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Yes, a maximum security prison.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What was it about her that you liked so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, she laughs at my jokes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "There must be moments in your relationship early on when you say -- honestly, I would love to have dinner next Wednesday, but I'm actually going to be in space?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Wednesday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Has it affected her ability to have a child?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well, we don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "It would be an incredible way to seal the recovery, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "It would be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "How is she right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "She's doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gabby"]}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "What would you be thanking, in particular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Well, that Gabby is alive, first of all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Really special moment, that, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "It was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What is the reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I would say neither.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Have any of his family made any attempt to contact you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Are you surprised at that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "You know, I'm -- you know, I don't spend a lot of time thinking about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "ELLY: As a family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Does Gabby have any thoughts towards the man that shot her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Well, you know, she doesn't spend a lot of time being angry about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Is that a fair reflection of how she is now in terms of being able to talk and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I'd say it is now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "What's your gut instinct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "So I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Have her politics changed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Has her view of gun control changed at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "You know, we haven't talked a lot about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "What do you think if Gabby was here she would say to people that they should be thankful for, given this life-changing thing she's been through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Well, certainly, you know, in her case, with one event having such a serious impact on her health, I think she'd remind people to be thankful, you know, for your health and for your family and, you know, for being alive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]